corkd.com 2010-05-16

# Cork’d Privacy Policy

This privacy policy (the " _Privacy Policy_ ") describes how Corkd treats the information (the " _Information_ ") that it collects from you when you use the Site and forms part of and is incorporated within Corkd's Terms and Conditions (the " _Terms_ "). As a reminder, you should review the Terms in connection with your use of the Corkd.com website (the " _Site_ "). Your use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of the Terms, including the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. In the event of any conflict, inconsistency or ambiguity between the Terms and this Privacy Policy, the Terms shall control. Capitalized Terms used in this Privacy Policy but not defined herein shall have the definition ascribed to such term in the Terms. Questions or comments regarding this privacy policy or any other aspect of the Site should be sent to our corporate offices at: CORKD, LLC, 12 Desbrosses Street, New York, NY 10013, Email: _[contact@corkd.com](mailto:contact@corkd.com)_.    

**Collection and Use of Information.**

When you register with Corkd to become an authorized User, you will be required to submit certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, gender and city of residence. We may also collect other Information from you from time to time including your username and password. Furthermore, after you have become an authorized User you may elect to voluntarily provide additional information to Corkd which may enable you to better identify yourself to other Corkd Users. You should note that your Information may be embodied or incorporated in your User Content (as defined in the Terms) and that this Privacy Policy shall not limit the rights granted by you in the Terms with respect to any User Content. You may always refuse to supply any Information with it being understood that such refusal may not allow you to access certain portions of the Site.    

We collect such Information to provide our users with a personalized interface. Additionally, Corkd or its affiliates and business partners (including certain wineries) may use your Information to market to you, and provide you with information about their products and services. We adhere to an opt-in/opt-out policy in communicating with our Users and thus, if you no longer desire to receive any such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribed instructions provided in any of the communications. Please note, however, that if you register as a User on the Site, you may not opt-out of receiving certain administrative and service-related messages.   

When Users visit and use the Site, the web-servers serving Corkd may automatically collect and record certain information about such User's use of the Site. Such information may include a User's IP address, the domain from which the User is using the Site, the web pages visited by the User and other information relating to the User's use of the Site. Such Information shall be used for administration purposes in connection with an internal review of User's use of the Site. [We also provide this Information (as well as information from third-party market researchers) about our Users on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers. Any Information provided by subscribers online as part of an advertiser promotion online (i.e. online coupons) may be provided directly to advertisers.] Please note that certain Information provided by you on the Site or created through your use of the Site must remain publicly available through the Site as it is viable to the community aspect of the Site.    

**Third Party Websites.**

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by Corkd. Corkd does not control the privacy policies of our affiliates and business partners which may be accessed, directly or indirectly, through the Site. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third party sites may be subject to the privacy of those sites, if any. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of the Information on these third party sites and Corkd is not to be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your Information by any other third party. You should also be aware that if you submit information to "forums", "chat-rooms" or other "message boards", such information may be deemed public information and you might lose any privacy rights you may have with respect to such information.   

**Cookies.**

Cookies are small bits of information that may be placed on your computer. Corkd uses cookies to identify your internet browser, store your preferences, and determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on the Site. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information. By adjusting settings on your browser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected. Third party websites linked to on the Site may also contain cookies. Corkd does not control these third party websites or cookies and Users of the Site should check the privacy policy of the third party website to see whether and how it uses cookies.    

**Other Service Providers.**

We hire third-party vendors to provide specialized services such as customer support, hosting, security, caching, email message deployment, suppression, merge and de-duplication services, data processing, and special products or services that you have requested. These companies are only allowed to use the Information in order to help us fulfill our services to you. We do not provide your Information to these companies for their own, permanent use.   

**Change in Control.**

We are always seeking to improve the Site and our business. In accomplishing these objectives, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our business family may merge with, sell all or substantially all of its assets to, or be acquired by another company. We may transfer some or all of your Information as a part of these or similar transactions in order that the service being provided to you may continue or for other business purposes.   

**Foreign Jurisdiction.**

When a Member who is located in a country other than the United States chooses to post User Content or Information that will be publicly disclosed, that User is responsible for ensuring that such Information or Content conforms to all local data protection laws. Corkd is not responsible under any privacy laws or local data protection laws in any jurisdiction other than the United States for any such posted information.

**Compliance with Laws.**

Corkd will disclose any Information to any government or law enforcement officials or private parties as Corkd shall determine, in its sole and absolute discretion, is necessary or appropriate to respond to any claim or to comply with any legal process to protect the rights of Corkd or any other third party or to comply with any international, federal, state or local law, regulation or ordinance or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or actionable activity. 

**Modification of Terms.**

From time to time Corkd may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect, among other things, changes in the law or our Information collection and use practices and such modifications shall be effective upon posting by Corkd on the Site. Your continued use of the Site after a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.

**Miscellaneous.**

Corkd uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information that you submit through the Site. You should be aware, however, that we make no representation or warranty that your information will be completely secure from loss or unauthorized access, use, interception or distribution.

Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the Information we collect about you. You may comment, or delete this Information by sending an e-mail to contact@corkd.com.
